themost10.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy

**The Most 10 respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of The Most 10.

**Credit card details**

Themost10.com will never ask your credit cart details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on themost10.com

**External Sites.**

The Most 10 is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at[ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Adsense ")

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows The Most 10 to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and The Most 10 does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to The Most 10 and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through The Most 10 have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email webmaster
